Kelly, Edward J. Papers 5867
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- 8 Hour Hassle (Folder 1 of 2), 1954 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- 8 Hour Hassle (Folder 2 of 2), 1954 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Council #33 DEN, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 17)
- Council 34 SFO, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 18)
- Council #52 LGH, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 19)
- Council #57 L19X, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 20)
- Council # 115 PDX, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 21)
- Dead Head Pay, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 22)
- CAA Take-A-Look, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 23)
- Aviation Medical Standards, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 24)
- Council # 27 SEA, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 25)
- Council # 12 CHI, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 26)
- Council # 5 EWR, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 27)
- MEC General 1954 (Box 15, Folder 28)
- Constitution and By-Laws ALPA Policy Manual an Negotiations Hand Book, 1953-1966 (Box 15, Folder 29)
- 1967-69 Agreement Between United Air Lines, Inc. and the Air Line Pilots 1969 Supplemental Agreement Between United Air Lines, Inc. and the Air Line Pilots, 1967-1969 (Box 15, Folder 30)
- 1974 Agreement Between United Air Lines, Inc. and the Air Line Pilots+ 1972 Supplemental Agreement Between United Air Lines, Inc. and the Air Line Pilots, 1972- 1974 (Box 15, Folder 31)
- 1970-1977Agreement Between United Air Lines, Inc. and the Air Line Pilots and 1972 Appendix (Box 15, Folder 32)
- The United Air Lines Representative Handbook Constitution and By-Laws, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 33)
- Addresses, Seniority List, Runholders, Schedule Rules and Allocation Report, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 34)
- Initial Report of the Benefit Policy Study Committee, 1956 (Box 15, Folder 35)
- Report and Recommendations of the Turbo Prop and Jet Study Committee, 1956 (Box 15, Folder 36)
- ALPA Training Plans Committee Report Ed Watson (EAL), 1958 (Box 15, Folder 37)
- The ALPA Story, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 38)
- Chapter III- Wes Wager's Dissertation Plus Unionization + Coll. Bargaining of Airline Pilots, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Report of Benefit Policy Study Committee, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Preliminary Report of the Benefit Policy Study Committee, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- The Leading Edge Vol. IV No. 1,1, Volume II No. 8, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- The Leading Edge Vol. IV No. III, IV, V, VI, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- The Leading Edge Vol. Iv, V No. II, VII, VIII, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- UAL Group Insurance Back to 1948 (Folder 1 of 2), 1948-1966 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- UAL Group Insurance Back to 1948 (Folder 2 of 2), 1948-1966 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- National Academy of Arbitrators and Other Documents, 1977-1978 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- National Academy of Arbitrators Members+ National Academy of Arbitrators 1978 Meeting (Box 16, Folder 10)
- 1972 Agreement between United Air Lines, Inc. and the Air Line Pilots 1974 Supplemental Agreement between United Airlines Inc. and the Air Line Pilots, 1972- 1974 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Fender/Pots (77-4) HK Snyder (77-7) The Chronicle, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Cox- Stear 76-11, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Photo of UAL Reps E.J. Kelly + H.F. Hill Mid 1950s (Box 16, Folder 14)
- ALPA Constitution and Bylaws, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Journal/ Binder (Box 16, Folder 16)